这样的表演才是人们想在
Now, this is exactly the type of performance you would expect to see
全国大学生无伴奏合唱锦标赛(ICCA)上所期望看到的
at the International Championship of Collegiate A Cappella.
我说得对不对 盖尔?
Am I right, Gail?
约翰 你说得太对了 对得不能再对了
John, you're so right, everything else seems wrong.
这帮来自巴顿大学的刺儿头小子们总能震撼评委
Boy, these Barden University Treblemakers always thrill the judges.
这屋子里的女士们真是兴奋得不得了
And the ladies in the room cannot get enough.
没错 约翰
So true, John.
也只有像男人一样唱歌的男孩才能让女人感觉如少女一般了
Nothing makes a woman feel more like a girl than a man who sings like a boy.
克洛伊 你看看你 简直一团糟 你一点都不尽心 实在是太靠不住了
Chloe, look at you. You're a mess. You're unfocused. You're unreliable.
嘴里的气味难闻死了 跟往常一样
And your breath smells like egg. Like, all the time.
真不敢相信我毕业后要把贝拉合唱团交给你们两个脓包
I can't believe the Bellas are being passed on to you two slut bags after we graduate.
你的独唱别给我弄砸了
Just don't eff up your solo.
我不会让你失望的
I won't disappoint you.
我爸爸常说 "如果你赢不了的话
My dad always says, "If you're not here to win,
就从科威特滚出去吧"
get the hell out of Kuwait."
你爸爸有没有告诉过让你闭嘴?
Has your dad ever told you to shut up?
我没事
I'm fine.
哦! 天啊 好疼啊
Ouch! Boy, that hurt.
多性感的男子劈叉啊
Sexy man-splits.
他的疼痛是我们的收获 盖尔
His pain is our gain, Gail.
没错 祝你们好运 伙计们!
All right, good luck, guys!
祝上场好运!
Good luck out there!
说真的 你们这群妞儿真得非常棒... 才怪
Seriously, you girls are awesome... ly horrible.
我恨你们 你们去死吧 女性万岁! 重友轻色的妞儿们!
I hate you. Kill yourselves. Girl power! Sisters before misters!
好了 姑娘们 机不可失 时不再来 加油!
All right, ladies, it's now or never. Hands in!
一 二...
One, two...
现在上场的是 巴顿大学的的贝拉合唱团!
Up now, the Barden Bellas!
贝拉合唱团今晚开创了历史
Well, the Bellas tonight are making history
她们是历史上第一支闯入ICCA决赛的女子合唱团
as the first ever all-female group to advance to the ICCA finals.
没错 约翰 你说为什么女子合唱团
That's right, John. Now, why do you think it's taken so long
要花那么长时间才能站在这个舞台上呢?
for an all-lady group to break through that a cappella glass ceiling?
盖尔 通常来说 女性很难发出低音
Well, Gail, the women, typically, cannot hit the low notes,
低音能为编排增色不少 从而能震撼评委
which really round out an arrangement, thrill the judges,
而在比赛中 这点恰恰是女性所欠缺的
and that can really hurt them in competition.
女的根本就不擅长无伴奏合唱 就跟她们不擅长当医生一样
Women are about as good at a cappella as they are at being doctors.
一 二 三 四
One, two, three, four.
是我感觉错了呢 还是我们刚刚真的左转到了瞌睡村?
Is it me or did we just take a left turn into Snoozeville?
是啊 而且我们还停在了未批准使用的地方
Yeah, and we parked in a lot where they do not validate.
- 不!  - 天啊...
- No!  - Holy...
这也太夸张了吧!
This is a surprise!
这事儿从没发生过! 现在 也只有这样你们
This has never happened! Now, this is how you bring some excitement
才能给无伴奏合唱大赛增加亮点了
to the International Championship of Collegiate A Cappella.
她吃了一星期的饭这下可全没了
She had a week's worth of lunch and lost it.
怎么没了 不都在地上呢
Well, she didn't lose it. We know exactly where it is.
- 前三排全是啊  - 太 太不可思议了...
- It's all over the third row.  - No, no...
-=圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/=-
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
完美音调
-=圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/=-
协调: 景鲤
翻译: 脸圆圆 我是羊 为化工攒人品 岸
校对: fabulous_carr 嘿疯
我自己来 谢谢
I got it. Thanks.
嗨! 欢迎来到巴顿大学 哪个宿舍楼?
Hi there! Welcome to Barden University. What dorm?
好像是贝克楼
Baker Hall, I think.
好的 那你顺着这条路一直走下去
Okay. So, what you're gonna do is you're gonna go down this way,
然后右拐 穿过双开门...
you're gonna take a right and you go through those double doors...
你的校园地图
Your campus map.
你的备用防狼口哨
And your official BU rape whistle.
没事的话千万别瞎吹
Don't blow it unless it's actually happening.
嘿
Hey.
你一定是金凯米 我是贝卡
You must be Kimmy Jin. I'm Beca.
不会说英语?
No English?
还是会说英语?
Yes English?
跟我说下你的英语是坏是好就行了
Just tell me where you're at with English.
他来了 我是本基 你一定是杰西吧
There he is. I'm Benji. You must be Jesse.
你在开玩笑吧 喔!
And you must be kidding. Wow!
把宿舍弄成这样可能有点过了
Looking at it now, I can see that it's a bit much.
我可以摘下来的
I can take it down.
不 别摘 我的意思是 我只是需要适应一小下
No, no way. I mean, it took a second for my eyes to adjust,
不过我可以接受
but I can roll with this.
其实 我只是想让你知道 我绝对不是个呆子
Look, just so you know, I'm not a total nerd.
我还很擅长近距离魔术
I also happen to be super into close-up magic.
老兄 真了不起!
Dude, that's awesome!
这小家伙藏在那里多久了?
How long was that little guy in there?
几天吧
Several days.
嘿 我是校警 把你们的冷酒器都藏好了
Hey, this is campus police. Hide your wine coolers.
不过是... 你老爹开个玩笑而已
Just... it's your old man making a funny.
注意 克里斯・洛克要登场了
Chris Rock, everybody.
嘿 你一定是贝卡的室友
Hey, you must be Beca's roommate.
我是米切尔博士 贝卡的爸爸
I'm Dr. Mitchell, Beca's dad.
我在这儿教比较文学
I teach Comparative Literature here.
你什么时候到这儿的? 你怎么过来的?
So, when did you get here? How did you get here?
打车来的 不想麻烦你和希拉
Took a cab. Didn't wanna inconvenience you and Sheila.
那个变态后妈怎么样了?
How is the stepmonster?
她很好 很谢谢你问候她 她去拉斯维加斯参加一个会议去了...
She is fine, thank you for asking. She's actually in Vegas at a conference...
不 老爸 我不是关心她 我只是想说 "变态后妈"
No, Dad, I don't actually care. I just wanted to say "stepmonster."
你们没到校园里玩一玩吗?
So, have you guys been out on the quad yet?
春天的时候 所有的学生都在草地上学习呢
In the springtime, all the students study on the grass.
我不想在草地上学习 老爸
I don't wanna study on the grass, Dad.
我要搬去洛杉矶 在唱片公司找份工作
I need to move to LA and get a job at a record label
然后自己养活自己
and start paying my dues.
又来了 你要知道 贝卡
Here we go again. You know, Beca,
你不能把DJ当工作 它不过是个爱好
DJing is not a profession, it's a hobby.
除非你是里克・蒂斯或者是其他什么很了不起的人
Unless you're Rick Dees or someone awesome.
不是这样... 我...
That's not... I...
我想做音乐 我想创作音乐 爸爸
I wanna produce music. I wanna make music, Dad.
但是你要先上完大学再说
But you're going to get a college education first.
再加一句 免费的 就这么定了
For free, I might add. End of story.
我要去游园会了
I'm going to the Activities Fair.
我也去 我要和我超级好的朋友金凯米一起去游园会了
Me, too. I'm going to the Activities Fair with my super-good friend, Kimmy Jin.
留下名字 留下电话 加入正义兄弟会
Taking names, taking numbers. Join our righteous frat.
不为朋友两肋插刀不算好兄弟
If you ain't pledging Sigma Beta, you ain't worth no crap.
- 那句话是双重否定  - 是多重否定
- That's a double negative.  - That's a lot of negatives.
跟我来 学校里只有一个社团是值得参加的
Follow me. There's only one group on this campus worth joining.
只要还在这个学校 这就是男生的终极幻想
As far as Barden goes, that's what being a man's all about.
刺儿头小子合唱团
The Treblemakers.
他们是无伴奏合唱的摇滚明星 是巴顿的救星
The rock stars of a cappella, the messiahs of Barden.
跟你说 他们不收运动员 兄弟会的人 或者很酷的人
Well, you know, not including athletes, frat guys, or actual cool people.
一群有组织的呆子唱歌 不错嘛
Organized nerd singing. This is great.
是的 就是这个意思 你唱歌怎么样?
Yeah, it makes so much sense. How's your voice?
哦 不错啊
Oh, nice.
我要不惜一切代价打垮这群怪人
I will stop at nothing to take those ding-a-lings down.
嘿 巴布 你今年想要试音吗? 我们要招人了
Hey, Barb. You gonna audition this year? We have openings.
现在你们的前途都被你吐没了
Now that you've puked your way to the bottom,
你才想起我?
you might actually consider me?
我三次试音确都没有被录取
I auditioned for you three times and never got in
就因为你说我的胸部像熏肠
because you said my boobs look like baloney.
大家都知道了 贝拉合唱团已经成了无伴奏合唱团的笑柄
The word's out. Bellas is the laughing stock of a cappella.
祝你们今年试音好运 傻逼们
Good luck auditioning this year. Douche-b's.
哦 天呐 这实在太滑稽了
Oh, my God. This is a travesty.
天啊 我们要是连香肠胸巴布都拉不到 那我们就拉不到任何人了
God, if we can't even recruit Baloney Barb, then we can't get anybody.
别小题大做好吗? 嗨 你想不想...
Just take the dramatics down a notch, okay? Hi, do you wanna...
就是你让我们陷入窘境的
Well, you're the one who got us into this hot mess.
我们会好起来的
We'll be fine.
我保证我们能找到
I am confident that we will find
八个身材巨好
eight super-hot girls with bikini-ready bodies
和音完美 音准绝佳的女孩 好吧?
who can harmonize and have perfect pitch. Okay?
嗨 你想不想成为我们的一员...
Hi, would you like to be a member of...
继续发传单 我们得坚持我们的传统
Just keep flyering. We have tradition to uphold.
我们就找唱歌好的人怎么样?
How about we just get good singers?
- 什么? 唱歌好的人?比如?  - 嗨
- What? Good singers? What?  - Hi.
- 你会唱歌吗?  - 会啊
- Can you sing?  - Yeah.
- 你会读谱子吗?  - 会啊
- Can you read music?  - Yeah.
- 你能唱高音吗?  - 试试吧
- Can you match pitch?  - Try me.
不错
Yeah.
这还真是个好开头
That was a really good start.
我是塔斯马尼亚岛最好的歌手 是有牙齿的歌手
I'm the best singer in Tasmania. With teeth.
- 我爱这个  - 你叫什么名字?
- Love it.  - What's your name?
胖艾米
Fat Amy.
唔... 你叫你自己胖艾米吗?
Um... you call yourself Fat Amy?
是的 这样像你们一样的瘦子们就不会在我背后说什么了
Yeah, so twig bitches like you don't do it behind my back.
试音时见 胖艾米
I will see you in auditions, Fat Amy.
我不但会唱歌 而且我还很擅长现代舞
I can sing but I'm also good at modern dance,
古典舞 还有人鱼舞
olden dance, and mermaid dancing,
人鱼舞略有些不同
which is a little different.
通常是从地上先开始的
You usually start on the ground.
哦
Ooh.
- 地板上的动作很多  - 我懂了
- It's a lot of floor work.  - I see that.
巴顿DJ社团
耶 DJ 犹太聋子
Yeah, DJs. Deaf Jews.
哦
Oh.
你们好!
Shalom!
这不算是个真正意义上的词 再努力点吧
That's not a real word but keep trying.
你们能做到的
You will get there.
你家乡没什么犹太人吗?
Not a lot of Jewish people where you're from?
啊...
Ah...
不是的 我高中的时候表演了屋顶上的提琴手
No. I did do Fiddler on the Roof, though, in high school.
是我 还有一些土著居民一起演的 完全是犹太风格的
It was, like, me and some Aboriginals. It was really Jewish.
绝对是犹太风格的
It was full-on Jew.
嘿 伙计们 这样吧 我给你们我的号码
Hey, guys. All right, I'll give you my number.
她怎么样?
What about her?
我不知道 她对于我们来说太另类了
I don't know. She looks a little too alternative for us.
嗨 有没有兴趣加入无伴奏合唱团?
Hi, any interest in joining our a cappella group?
哦 不错 这看起来还像那么回事儿
Oh, right, this is, like, a thing now.
太棒了 我们翻唱歌曲 但完全不用乐器
Totes. We sing covers of songs but we do it without any instruments.
全靠我们的嘴发声
It's all from our mouths.
是嘛
Yikes.
学校有四支合唱团 贝拉合唱团 也就是我们 我们是最突出的
There's four groups on campus. The Bellas. That's us. We're the tits.
比优和声团
The BU Harmonics.
他们唱很多麦当娜的歌
They sing a lot of Madonna.
那边的高音合唱团
The High Notes.
他们不是很上进
They're not particularly motivated.
然后还有...
And then there's...
那么 你有没有兴趣呢?
So, are you interested?
不好意思 这也太无聊了吧
Sorry, it just, it's pretty lame.
你说什么?
A-ca-scuse me?
女士和着玛丽亚凯莉的榜单歌曲整齐地跳舞怎么就无聊了
Synchronized lady dancing to a Mariah Carey chart topper is not lame.
我们在很多地方演唱 还参加全国锦标赛
We sing all over the world and we compete in national championships.
有目的的?
On purpose?
我们在柯布能源表演艺术中心表演过 你个小贱人!
We played the Cobb Energy Performing Arts Centre, you bitch!
哦!
Oh!
奥布里的意思是说我们是个有组织
What Aubrey means to say is that we are a close-knit,
有才气的女性合唱团
talented group of ladies whose dream is
目标是冲进今年在林肯中心举办的全国总决赛
to return to the national finals at Lincoln Center this year.
能不能帮我们实现梦想呢?
Help us turn our dreams into a reality?
对不起 我不唱歌 不过真的很高兴见到你们
Sorry, I don't even sing, but it was really nice to meet you guys.
我们该怎么办?
What are we gonna do?
你进来的时候竟让还弹着吉他
When you came in and you were just strumming the guitar,
而且还都不在调上 我当时真想掐死你!
and it was, like, totally off-key, I wanted to choke you!
- 邦博尔  - 我真想让你滚蛋!
- Bumper.  - I wanted to choke you out!
我准备过去自我介绍一下
Okay, I'm gonna go introduce myself.
表现的自然一些 跟平常一样
Everybody be cool. It's just a normal day.
- 嗨  - 嗨
- Hi.  - Hi.
我是本杰明・爱普巴姆
Benjamin Applebaum.
三年前我在美国购物中心看过你们的演出
I saw you guys perform at a Mall of America like three years ago.
那真的改变了我的生命 从那以后我无时无刻不想着你们
Totally changed my life. I have not stopped thinking about you since.
谢谢了
Thank you. Yeah.
还有邦博尔 我是你的超级粉丝
And, Bumper, huge fan.
你唱的爱之匙合唱团的"你可相信魔力"
Your arrangement of Lovin' Spoonful's Do You Believe in Magic
激励我成为一名合格的魔术师
inspired me to become a certificated illusionist.
哇哦
Wow.
你的怪异已经影响到我的声带了
The smell of your weird is actually affecting my vocal cords,
所以我希望你赶快走吧 快走
so I'm gonna need you to scoot. Skedaddle.
不如我们互相留下邮箱地址
But why don't we just exchange emails,
有空可以一起去逛逛怎么样?
and then totally hang out right now, together?
不 不能接受 不能接受
No. Hard pass. Hard pass.
真是个呆子 好了 伙计们 现在我们来合一下音调
What a nerd alert. Okay, guys, now let's match pitch.
- 太过分了  - 你觉得呢?
- Too far.  - You think?
是的 我是不是应该变另外一个魔术?
Yeah. Should I have done another trick?
不 我觉得你的魔术很不错 我只是话说得很奇怪
No, I think your trick was fine. I just think the talking was a little weird.
也许你可以在Facebook上给他发信息
Maybe you can try to Facebook message him.
嘿 我是贝卡
Hey, I'm Beca.
- 在那边  - 谢谢
- Over there.  - Thanks.
95.7 WBUJ 独立思想的音乐
Ninety-five point seven, WBUJ, music for the independent mind.
- 嘿  - 嗨
- Hey.  - Hi.
你在这儿站了很久了吗?
Have you been standing there long?
不 没有 我刚到这儿 没站多久
No. No, I just got here, I wasn't just standing here.
新生不许进来 不好意思
Freshmen aren't allowed in the booth. Sorry.
我是卢克 播音站站长 你一定是那个叫贝卡的实习生吧?
I'm Luke. Station manager. You must be Becky the intern?
那个...
It's...
嘿 伙计 你们好吗? 我是杰西
Hey, man, what's up? I'm Jesse.
我是卢克 你迟到了
I'm Luke. You're late.
嘿 我知道你
Hey. I know you.
- 你不知道  - 我知道的
- No, you don't.  - Yeah, I do.
- 他不认识我  - 绝对认识她
- He doesn't.  - Totally know her.
好吧 不错 你们整理CD的时候可以搞清楚这件事情
Okay, cool. Well, you guys can figure it out while you're stacking CDs.
整理好了以后 还有事要注意
When you're done, there's more.
从现在开始 你们休息的时间会经常在一起 所以拜托
Now, you guys will be spending a lot of down time together, so please, just
别在桌子上做爱就好了
no sex on the desk.
我以前被烧伤过
I've been burned before.
我真的认得你 我还冲你唱过歌 因为你当时在出租车上 所以我记得你
I do know you. I sang to you. I remember because you were in a taxi.
- 等等 你爸爸是出租车司机吗?  - 不是
- Wait, is your dad a taxi driver?  - No.
哦
Oh.
我不想做这活儿 我想做音乐
This sucks. I wanted to play music.
我不是 我在这儿只有一个理由 我真的超爱整理CD
Not me. I'm here for one reason only. I really love stacking CDs.
你是怎么回事儿呢?
So, what's your deal?
你是那种黑暗又神秘的女孩儿
You one of those girls who's all dark and mysterious,
喜欢摘掉眼镜 喜欢带超恐怖的耳钉
then she takes off her glasses and that amazingly scary ear spike
然后你就意识到 她总是那么得漂亮
and you realize that, you know, she was beautiful the whole time.
- 我不戴眼镜  - 所以说你跟我描述的也差不多了
- I don't wear glasses.  - Then you're halfway there.
贝卡
Beca.
贝卡 醒醒
Beca, wake up.
真有趣 你这不像是要去上哲学课啊
Funny, this doesn't look like your Intro to Philosophy class.
那我就问你一个很重要的哲学问题
I'm posing an important philosophical question.
如果我不去上课 那课还会那么恶心吗?
If I don't actually go to that class, will it still suck?
听着 宝贝 大学是... 是非常棒的
Look, honey. College is... it's great.
你得在这里制造些回忆 我每天都看着呢
You get to create memories here, I see it every day.
你得给它一个机会
You just have to give it a chance.
你已经在这儿 多久了 有一个月了吧? 你有朋友吗?
You've been here, what, a month now? Do you have any friends?
- 金凯米是我的朋友  - 我不是
- Kimmy Jin is my friend.  - No.
你得走出去 贝卡 你得尝试一些东西
You gotta get out there, Bec. You gotta try something.
我在播音站找了份工作
I got a job at the radio station.
哦 那地方不错
Oh, great, that place.
又黑又脏而且 貌似还有三个怪人在那儿工作?
Yeah, it's dark and dirty and has like, what, those three weirdos who work there?
现在是四个了
Well, four now.
你得去尝试些新东西 贝卡 参加一个学校社团
You gotta try something new, Bec. Join one club on campus.
还有 如果一年以后 你还是不想待在这
And if, at the end of a year, you still don't wanna be here,
你还想去洛杉矶当吹牛老爹什么的(美国饶舌歌手)
you still wanna go off to LA and be P. Diddy,
好吧 那时候你可以退学
well, then, you can quit college.
而且我会帮你搬去洛杉矶
And I will help you move to LA.
- 你说真的吗?  - 是的 认真的
- Seriously?  - Yes, seriously.
但是我必须要看到你的行动 贝卡
But I really need to see it, Beca.
这是大学 好好享受吧
This is college. Join in.
- 你会唱歌!  - 天啊!
- You can sing!  - Dude!
- 你能唱多高?  - 我什么?
- How high does your belt go?  - My what?
- 哦 我的天!  - 你必须去贝拉合唱团试音
- Oh, my God!  - You have to audition for the Bellas.
在你把帘子拉上之前我都听不进你讲的任何话
I can't concentrate on anything you're saying until you cover your junk.
你就考虑一下吧
Just consider it.
有一次我们为王子唱和声
One time, we sang backup for Prince.
他的屁股是那么的小 就好像 我一只手就能握住
His butt is so tiny that I can hold it with, like, one hand.
喔! 哦!
Oops! Oh!
你不是来真的吧 我裸着呢
Seriously. I am nude.
你刚刚在唱《钛合金》 对不对?
You were singing Titanium, right?
- 你知道大卫・库塔?  - 我是不是喜欢摇滚乐? 当然
- You know David Guetta?  - Have I been living under a rock? Yeah.
这歌是我的最爱
That song is my jam.
我女性血液（月经血）
My lady-jam.
真不错
That's nice.
是的 那歌真的给了我力量
It is. That song really builds.
- 好吧  - 你可以唱给我听吗?
- Gross.  - Can you sing it for me?
不行 出去!
Dude, no. Get out!
不是为了那个原因 你不唱的话我就不出去 你自己看...
Not for that reason. I'm not leaving here till you sing. So...
哦 是的 我对我的身材很自信
Oh, yeah. I'm pretty confident about all this.
你身材确实不错
You should be.
哦!
Oh!
我还得洗澡
Still need to shower.
你声音很不错
You have a lovely voice.
谢谢
Thanks.
哦
Oh.
试音时见哦!
Yeah. See you at auditions!
关于试音 你们每个人要唱十六个小节的
For your audition, each of you will be singing sixteen bars
凯利・克拉克森的"既然你已离开"
of Kelly Clarkson's Since You've Been Gone.
如果有乐团喜欢你 他们会直接联系你的
If a group likes you, they will contact you directly.
我的乐盲伙伴贾斯丁会收集你们的信息
My tone-deaf sidekick Justin here will be collecting your information.
如果我能用正常人的方式 唱哪怕就那么一小点儿
If I could sing a lick, in any human way possible,
我也会唱 但是我真的不行
I would, but I can't.
- 而且我因此每天都痛恨着自己!  - 我知道
- And I hate myself every day because of it!  - I know.
不过如果你觉得这只是什么高中的学校俱乐部
But if you think this is just some high school club,
觉得你可以自顾自的唱唱跳跳来解决社会问题
where you can sing and dance your way through any big social issue,
或是懵懂的性冲动
or confused sexuality,
那你来错地方了
you have come to the wrong place.
这地方不接受以上任何一种人
There is none of that here.
那个是高中
That's high school.
这玩意儿才是真正的生活!
This shit is real life!
现在 别光说不做了 开唱吧 都给我秀出来
Now, don't just bring it, sing it. And let's do this.
嘿 贝拉合唱团 还记不记的你在大联盟比赛时吐得情景?
Hey, Bellas, remember when you tried to play in the big leagues and you choked?
大家都要吸取那个教训
That should really be a lesson to everyone.
如果你每天都唱那无聊的 女里女气的垃圾歌
If you sing the same boring, girly shit every year,
你还会吐的 吐得到处都是
you will blow chunks. All over the place.
满地都是呕吐物
Vomit everywhere.
我的伙伴
My fellow a-ca-people.
我们不会让任何自大的 傲慢的混球
We will not let egotistical, big-headed, garbage dirtballs,
来挡我们的道 不管你是谁
whoever you may be, get in our way.
我保证
I promise you,
我们会重回锦标赛并且完成我们去年表演的歌曲
we will return to the ICCAs and finish what we started last year.
这是第一个选手 祝你好运
And here's the first one up. Good luck.
准备好就可以开始了 老兄
Whenever you're ready, dude.
好的 嗨 我叫辛西娅・罗丝
Yeah, hi, my name is Cynthia Rose.
不是男的 不是男的
Not a dude. It's not a dude.
没有伴舞? 好吧
There's no backup dancers? Okay.
你们好 我叫莉莉・奥库拉玛拉 我有像鱼一样的鱼鳃骨
Hello. My name is Lilly Onakuramara. I have gills like a fish.
不好意思 你说什么?
I'm sorry. What was that?
你们好 我叫莉莉・奥库拉玛拉 我有像鱼一样的鱼鳃骨
Hello. My name is Lilly Onakuramara. I was born with gills like a fish.
一 二 三 四
One, two, three, four.
哦
Oh.
嗨 大家好 我是斯蒂西
Hi, everybody, my name is Stacie.
我的爱好有角质护理和看电视
My hobbies include cuticle care and the E! Network.
真得好高
It's high.
天呐
Jesus.
呃啊!
Ugh!
谢谢
Thank you.
现场表演让我有点紧张
Performing live gives me such a rush.
搞定
Crushed it.
好了 大家都表演完了 今年真的没给我留下什么印象 伙计们
Okay. That is everybody. I'm really not that impressed this year, guys.
哦 等等 还有一个
Oh, wait, there's one more.
嗨
Hi.
你好
Hello.
呃...
Um...
我不知道我们得准备歌曲
I didn't know we had to prepare that song.
哦 没关系 随便唱什么都行
Oh, that's okay. Sing anything you want.
呃...
Uh...
- 可以拿吗?  - 哦好
- May I?  -  Oh.
哇哦
Wow.
女高音 杰西卡 玛丽・伊莉丝 莉莉
The sopranos. Jessica, Mary Elise, Lilly.
中音 辛西娅・罗丝 斯蒂西 科瑞
The mezzos. Cynthia Rose, Stacie, Kori.
还有我们的低音 胖艾米 丹妮丝 艾什莉 和贝卡
And our altos. Fat Amy, Denise, Ashley, and Beca.
你们先喝下你们面前的姐妹之血 然后我们再开始
We shall begin by drinking the blood of the sisters that came before you.
- 拜托 我不要  - 别担心 这是布恩农场(美国一种苹果酒)
- Dude, no.  - Don't worry, it's Boone's Farm.
好了 看看谁能唱高音
Well, well, well, look who's in treble.
- 啊 经典的双关  - 是啊
- Ah, classic pun.  - I know.
没有本基?
No Benji?
现在 把你们的丝巾放在右手上
Now, if you'll place your scarves in your right hand.
我 唱出自己的名字...
I, sing your name...
我...
I...
承诺履行作为贝拉成员的责任和义务
promise to fulfill the duties and responsibilities of a Bella woman.
并庄严宣誓 绝不与刺儿头小子上床
And I solemnly promise to never have sexual relations with a Treblemaker
如违此誓 将被野狼撕破喉咙 声断命绝
or may my vocal cords be ripped out by wolves.
并庄严宣誓 绝不与刺儿头小子上床
And I solemnly promise to never have sexual relations with a Treblemaker
如违此誓 将被野狼撕破喉咙 声断命绝
or may my vocal cords be ripped out by wolves.
现在你们是贝拉的一员啦
You are all Bellas now.
大功告成
We did it.
我还想再喝点儿这个
I want some more of this.
是吗?
Did we?
姐妹们 欢迎来到阿卡贝拉无伴奏合唱迎新晚会
Ladies, welcome to a-ca-initiation night.
准备好迷倒众生吧
Prepare to soften the beach.
我都不知道来这里干什么
I don't know what I'm doing here.
美梦成真了 我这样性感丰满的大屁股也能混入这个圈子
Just living the dream. I still can't believe they let my sexy fat ass in.
贝卡! 贝卡!
Beca! Beca!
哇
Wow.
贝卡卡! 贝卡卡.
Be-caw! Be-caw.
真不敢相信自己的眼睛 你加入了巴顿贝拉合唱团?
Do my eyes deceive me or are you a Barden Bella?
- 是的  - 你是一个阿卡贝拉女歌手
- No.  - You're one of those a cappella girls,
我是一个阿卡贝拉男歌手 我俩会生下一个阿卡贝拉宝宝
I'm one of those a cappella boys, and we're gonna have a-ca-children.
- 命中注定的  - 你喝高了吧
- It's inevitable.  - You're really drunk right now.
等你酒醒后肯定全都不记得了
I don't think you're gonna remember any of this.
不 我一点儿都没醉 你没弄清楚状况
No. I'm not drunk at all, you're just blurry.
- 你没事吧? 嗯?  - 嗯
- You okay? Yeah?  - Yeah.
- 你还站得稳吗?  - 我可以...
- You almost fell over?  - You know, I could...
- 你现在能通过酒精测试吗?  - 可以
- Can you pass a sobriety test right now?  - Yep.
- 你能站得直吗?  - 看我这不就站直了吗?
- Can you stand up straight?  - See how I come right back?
我站直了 好了
And I come right back. Right. Wow.
要喝点儿什么吗?
Can I get you a drink?
可以啊
It sounds great.
- 我这就去给你拿  - 去吧
- I'm gonna get you a drink.  - Go for it.
你得融入这个氛围
I think you need to get on this level.
小心点儿
Please be careful.
嗨
Hi.
认识你真高兴
I am so glad that I met you.
相信我们很快就能非常合拍的
I think that we're gonna be really fast friends.
- 是啊 我都被你看光光了...  - 是啊
- Yeah. Well, you saw me naked, so...  - Yeah.
哼哼 妹子们 成群结队 准备看好戏了
Yeah. Yeah, ladies. Gather around. Ready for a show.
- 来吧 小妞们 排排站  - 来吧
- Come on, baby bubble, wait in line. Yep. - Yeah.
- 你们就爱看这个  - 我知道你们爱看
- You want some of this.  - I know you do.
- 很好  - 邦博尔和唐纳德
- Nice.  - Bumper and Donald.
粉墨登场
Getting it.
我们一共十来个人
You know, so there's like 10 of us.
也就是说 我们中间很可能有一个拉拉
That means that one of us is probably a lesbian.
是吗? 你觉得是哪个?
You think? Which one do you think it is?
我打赌是那个黑妞
My money's on Black Beauty.
要是我今晚喝多了
So, when I drink too much tonight,
我喝吐时你能帮我挽起头发吗?
can I count on you to hold my hair back if I puke?
啊
Ah.
别告诉她是我说的
Don't tell her I said that.
好了 我要去拿点儿喝的 来点儿麦啤补充活力
All right. I'm gonna go get a drink. This ginger needs her jiggle juice.
- 回见  - 悠着点儿
- See you later.  - Make good choices.
我为这个发型想出了一个新名字
I thought of a new name for this hairstyle.
叫正统犹太教马尾
It's called the Orthodox Jew ponytail.
是吗?
Yeah?
- 因为前面比较正常...  - 对哦
- 'Cause it's very reserved at the front...  - I see that.
- 但后面很夸张  - 我注意到两鬓留长的头发了
- But party in the back.  - I see these happening here.
关键问题是
Here's the real question.
跟谁上床更容易?
Who would be easier to sleep with?
美国队长还是大白鲨?
Captain America or a great white shark?
- 大白鲨 我可不会...  - 嘿
- Great white shark. I wouldn't...  - Hey.
你们两个浑球在聊什么呢?
What are you turd burgers talking about?
穿衣打扮吗?
Dressing for comfort?
你是我见过的最恶心的人了
You are probably the grossest human being I've ever seen.
你也不过就是个潘
Well, you're no panty-dropper yourself.
我有种跟你深情一吻的冲动
So I have a feeling that we should kiss.
这种冲动是好事还是坏事呢?
And is that feeling a good feeling or an incorrect feeling?
有时候我会有尝试冰毒的冲动
Well, I sometimes have a feeling I can do crystal meth,
- 但随后一想 "还是算了吧"  - 是啊
- but then I think, "Hmm. Better not."  - Yeah.
# 我无法用言语表达 但我可以... #
# I don't know the words, but I can... #
谢谢
Thank you.
太爽了
This is awesome.
确实不同凡响
It's definitely something.
我们就是校园之王!
We are the kings of campus!
哇 贝拉老成员真漂亮!
Man, the old Bellas was hot!
是啊 她们身材真棒
Yeah, they kept it tight.
好了 女高音站前面 女低音站后面
Okay. Sopranos in the front and altos in the back.
大家都看到了 科瑞没来
As you can see, Kori is not here.
因为她昨晚跟刺儿头小子搞上了
Last night she was Treble-boned.
她被逐出了贝拉团队
She has been disinvited from the Bellas.
入会誓言是认真的啊?
That oath was serious?
南方小鸡(美国德州乡村音乐组合)可不是闹着玩的
Dixie Chicks serious.
你可以跟任何人胡搞 就是刺儿头小子不行
You can fool around with whoever you want to, just not a Treble.
这就难办了 他们可都是少女杀手啊
That's not gonna be easy. He's a hunter.
你这么快被他们迷住了?
You call it a dude?
斯蒂西 刺儿头小子很鄙视我们
Stacie, the Trebles don't respect us,
如果让他们"插"进来的话
and if we let them penetrate us,
他们就会从我们这里吸取能量
we are giving them our power.
用"插"这个词不太好吧
Not a good enough reason to use the word "penetrate."
那么 有人要坦白吗?
So, does anyone here have anything to confess?
那是个意外 我...
It was an accident. I...
交出你的丝巾 然后走人
Turn in your scarf and go.
婊子
Slut.
把椅子带走
Take your chair.
有这个必要吗?
Was that necessary?
这是一场战争 贝卡
This is war, Beca,
我的职责是保证我的士兵们做好准备背水一战
and it is my job to make sure that my soldiers are prepped at go time
我会挑出三首好歌并精心编排做到尽善尽美
with three kick-ass songs sung and choreographed to perfection.
离地区分赛只剩四个月了
And there are only four months until regionals.
如果你们谁对我的管理贝拉的方式有意见
So, if you have a problem with the way that I run the Bellas,
那么就...
then you should just...
别太大压力 奥布里 放轻松
Don't stress, Aubrey. Relax.
我们可不想去年的事再次发生
We don't want a repeat of what happened last year.
去年发生了什么事?
What happened last year?
你说什么?
What are you saying?
去年发生了什么事?
What happened last year?
你们想看去年的现场表演吗?
And do you guys wanna see a dead body?
点开"某男吐在了猫身上"
Click on "Guy Pukes on Cat."
够了!这事过去了
Enough! It happened. It's over.
我们每天都要排练至少两个小时 一周七天皆是如此
We will practice every day for at least two hours, seven days a week.
而且你们要增加有氧锻炼
And I trust you will add your own cardio.
- 有氧锻炼?  - 不要 有氧运动别算上我
- Why cardio?  - Yeah, no, don't put me down for cardio.
好了 我们继续
Okay, moving on.
这是一张清单 列出了我们翻唱过的所有歌曲
This is a list of all of the songs that we have ever performed.
请注意 我们只翻唱由女歌手唱红的曲目
And you will notice that we only do songs made famous by women.
一首本世纪的歌都没有
There's nothing from this century on here.
因为我们绝不偏离传统路线
Because we don't stray from tradition.
好了 这是我们夺冠计划
Now, this is how we will become champions.
贝拉的成功要素
麦克风使用技能
曲目精选集
交往对象禁止刺儿头小子
最终胜利!
加油 姐妹们! 跑起来!
Come on, girls! Let's go!
快快快! 抬起腿来!
Go, go, go! Pick up your knees!
快点儿 快点儿! 一二一二一二!
Faster, faster! One, two, one, two, one, two!
抬高腿 抬高腿! 跑起来! 加油
Knees up, knees up! Go, go! Go! Let's get it.
克洛伊 好样的 艾米!
Yes, Chloe. Nice. Amy!
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
我在练横向跑步
I'm doing horizontal running.
横向跑步?
Horizontal running?
停
No.
不行
No, no.
不要这样
No.
我知道... 我会做
I know... I can do it.
五 六 七 八
Five, six, seven, eight.
好了 到此结束
Okay, I'm calling it.
谢天谢地 三个小时前我就说过想上厕所了
Thank God. I asked to go to the bathroom three hours ago.
没听到 我一个字都没听到
Nothing. I hear nothing.
嘿 奥布里 我们刚刚排练的是那段录像里的舞蹈吗?
Hey, Aubrey. Did we just learn the same choreography from that video?
好了 别忘了拿好你们的演出日程表
Okay. Don't forget to pick up your performance schedules.
我们下周有个演出 没错 就是下周
We have a gig next week. That's right. Next week.
听着 是SBT兄弟会的年度秋季联谊会
You guys, it's the Sigma Beta Theta's Annual Fall Mixer.
好了 伸出手 姐妹们
Okay. Hands in, Bellas.
伸出手 阿卡妞儿们!
Hands in, a-ca-bitches!
数到三唱"啊"...
Sing "ah" on three...
啊!
Ah!
不不不 是数到三才唱 胖艾米
No, no, no. It's actually on three, Fat Amy.
啊
Ah.
好了 数到三哦
All right. On three.
一 二...
One, two...
好吧 我们下次排练的第一件事就是搞定这个
Okay, we will work on that first thing next time.
- 好了 散会  - 谢谢 再见
- Okay, guys. - Thank you. Goodbye.
她的手跟男人手似的
She has man hands.
贝卡 跟你说个事?
Beca, a word?
怎么了?
What's up?
秋季联谊会演出时你得把耳朵上那些乱七八糟的玩意给摘了
You know you'll have to take those ear monstrosities out for the Fall Mixer.
其实你很讨厌我对吧?
You really don't like me, do you?
- 我不喜欢你的态度  - 你又不了解我
- I don't like your attitude.  - You don't even know me.
我知道你对杰西有意思
I know you have a toner for Jesse.
什么?
A what?
有意思
A toner.
你被他迷住了 迎新会那晚我看见了 那会让你分心
A musical boner. I saw it at Hood Night. It's distracting.
那没什么大不了 你又不是我的老板 所以...
Yeah, that's not a thing and you're not the boss of me. So...
你可是发过誓的
You took an oath.
今天那个誓言已经害你少了两个成员
That oath cost you two girls already today.
我相信现在是你需要我 而不是我需要你
I'm pretty sure you need me more than I need you.
从你的裤子上的反应来看 我就知道你对他有意思
I can see your toner through those jeans.
那是我的老二
That's my dick.
你没事吧?
Everything okay?
我们最好能好好备战SBT的联谊会演出
We better have our shit together for SBT.
我不担心 我觉得我们肯定会很出色的
I'm not worried. I think we're gonna be a-ca-awesome.
这表演把我的啤酒都给糟蹋了
This makes my beer taste bad.
我看不下去了
I'm gonna stop this.
喂 喂 停住 停下来
Whoa, whoa. Just stop. Stop.
对不起 豪伊 我知道我们没准备好
I am so sorry, Howie. I know we're not performance ready.
我要的是惊艳的贝拉 而不是这样不入流的乌合之众
I wanted the hot Bellas, not this barnyard explosion.
- 我不会为这个出钱的 走吧  - 天呐
- I'm not paying for this. Let's go. Come on.  - God.
我希望你们每个人都记住现在的感受
Well, I hope you all remember the way you feel right now,
下次就不会再想重蹈覆辙了
so you will never wanna feel this way again.
克洛伊 你的嗓子一点儿都不像克里斯蒂娜・阿奎莱拉(美国流行女歌手)
Chloe, your voice didn't sound Aguilerian at all.
克洛伊 说真的 你出什么毛病了?
Chloe, for serious, what is wrong with you?
我有了结节
I have nodes.
- 什么? 天呐  - 我今天早上诊断出来的
- What? Oh, my God.  - I found out this morning.
结节是什么?
What are nodes?
声带囊肿
Vocal nodules.
是由于用嗓过度 声带摩擦过多
The rubbing together of your vocal cords at above-average rates
没有适当的休息而形成的
without proper lubrication.
它们长气管上 是梦想杀手
They sit on your windpipe and they crush your dreams.
那岂不是很疼吗? 那你为什么还要演出?
Isn't that painful? Why would you keep performing?
因为我喜欢唱歌
Because I love to sing.
没错 就像我的妇科医生嘱咐我一个半月之内不能有性生活
Yeah, it's like when my lady doctor told me not to have sex for six weeks,
我可没管那么多
and I did it anyway.
你真的应该听医生的话
You should really listen to your doctor.
好在诊断得早
The key is early diagnosis.
我有结节 但我还活着
I am living with nodes.
我是不会被打倒的
But I am a survivor.
我不得不唱低音了 因为我音域受到了限制
I just have to pull back. Because I am limited.
因为我有结节
Because I have nodes.
克洛伊 这真是太糟糕了
Chloe, this is horrible.
还好不是长疱疹了
Well, at least it's not herpes.
还是你也得了疱疹?
Or do you have that as well?
嗯?
Hmm?
- 杰西?  - 嗯
- Jesse?  - Yeah.
我饿了 你能不能...
I'm starving, so could you...
你想让我给你买午饭?
You want me to get you lunch?
你最好别再吃汉堡包了
You should probably lay off the burgers.
你再吃啤酒肚就出来了
You're not gonna be 22 forever, you know.
我觉得我还行吧
Yeah, I think I'm good.
他很棒 你很棒
He's good. You're good.
咱们走着瞧好了
And the chess match continues.
对了 这是我新做的混音
Hey, this is my new mix,
想放点儿什么音乐的话可以...
so if there's anything you wanted to play...
好的 有空我会放的
Yeah, okay, I'll put it on the pile.
好的
Okay.
你好吗 怪咖?
What's up, weirdo?
- 你要干嘛?  - 尽管我很喜欢
- What's this?  - As much as I love
跟你一起整理CD... 真的
spending time with you stacking CDs... and I do.
真的很喜欢 喜欢得要命
I love it, like, more than life.
我觉得我们还可以做些别的好玩的事
I figured we could do some other fun things
不然就无聊得要死了 对吧?
that don't make us wanna kill ourselves, right?
- 对的  - 所以 我带了些电影过来
- Yeah.  - So, brought some movies.
有"大白鲨" "外星人" "早餐俱乐部" "星球大战" "洛奇"
Jaws, E.T., The Breakfast Club, Star Wars and Rocky.
都是最佳配乐 原声带超棒的电影
Best scored and soundtracked movies of all time.
这是我长大后想做的事 我想为电影配乐
That's what I wanna do when I grow up. I wanna score movies.
令人感动流泪 让人震撼惊叹
Bring people to tears, you know. Blow their minds.
我觉得只有音乐才能做到
I feel like only music can do that.
是啊
Yeah.
你的女朋友肯定被你迷得神魂颠倒
You must really sweep your girlfriend off her feet.
我没有女朋友
I don't have a girlfriend.
- 什么?  - 没有
- What?  - No.
可你都买了袋装果汁还推荐看"洛奇" 啊
You have juice pouches and Rocky.
好吧 你想先看哪个?
Okay, so what do you wanna watch first?
我们能做点儿别的吗?
Wanna do something else?
我们可以体验父母离婚的感觉
We could relive my parents' divorce.
或者一起去看妇科医生
Or visit a gynecologist.
怎么 你不喜欢看电影吗?
What, do you not like movies or something?
什么电影都不爱看吗? 你怎么...
Like, any movies? You don't...
你到底是怎么了? 你怎么能不喜欢看电影呢?
What the hell is wrong with you? How do you not like movies?
不喜欢看电影就像不喜欢小狗一样
Not liking movies is like not liking puppies.
电影是不错 我只是觉得看电影很无聊 从来没坚持到结局
They're fine. I just get bored and never make it to the end.
结局是最精彩的部分
The endings are the best part.
我都能猜到结局是怎样的 比如 有情人终成眷属
They're predictable. Like, the guy gets the girl,
小孩看到了去世的人 达斯・维达是卢克的爸爸("星球大战"中主要角色)
and that kid sees dead people and Darth Vader is Luke's father.
哦 是吗 你只是随便猜测历史上最大制作电影的悬疑结局?
Okay, right, so you just happened to guess the biggest cinematic reveal in history?
"维达"在德语里意思是父亲
"Vader" in German means father.
他名字的字面意思是"达斯・父亲"
His name is literally "Darth Father".
那么 你懂德语
So, you know German.
现在我明白你为什么不喜欢好玩的东西了
Well, now I know why you don't like fun things.
你需要接受一次电影大扫盲
You know, you need a movie education.
你得被电影化 我来给你扫盲
You need a movie-cation. And I'm gonna give it to you.
得了吧 没完没了的贝拉排练就够我受的了
Yeah, in between Bella rehearsals, which are always.
你们准备好参加歌曲接龙了吗?
Are you guys getting ready for the riff-off?
歌曲接龙是什么玩意?
What the hell is a riff-off?
嗨起来!
Hit it!
欢迎来到歌曲接龙!
Welcome to the riff-off!
有谁准备好来一曲了吗?
Who's ready to get vocal?
获胜者将会得到超棒的奖品
The winners get the greatest prize of all.
我要打败你
I'm taking you down.
- 好把戏合唱团(加州摇滚乐团)用过的麦克风...  - 我不在乎
- The microphone used by Hoobastank...  - I don't care.
他们曾在在施内演艺中心演唱会上用过这只麦克风
when they rocked out at the Schnee Performing Arts Center.
我们看下第一个主题
Let's see our first category.
80年代女歌星
Ladies of the '80s.
《米奇》  - 唐妮贝西
Oh Mickey - Toni Basil
# 哦 米奇 你真帅 帅到我情难自禁 #
# Oh, Mickey, you're so fine you're so fine, you blow my mind #
# 嘿 米奇 嘿 米奇 #
# Hey, Mickey. Hey, Mickey #
# 哦 米奇 你真帅... #
# Oh, Mickey, you're so fine... #
《宛如处女》  - 麦当娜
Like a Virgin - Madonna
# 你如此迷人 你属于我 #
# You're so fine and you're mine #
# 我将属于你 直到永远 #
# I'll be yours till the end of time #
# 因为你让我感到 #
# 'Cause you made me feel #
# 是的 你让我感到 #
# Yeah, you made me feel #
# 闪闪发亮 如获新生 #
# So shiny and new #
# 宛如处女 #
# Like a virgin #
好了 姐妹们
Okay, guys.
# 像第一次般怦然心动 #
# Touched for the very first time #
《放马过来》  - 佩特・班纳塔
Hit Me With Your Best Shot - Pat Benatar
# 你曾伤了我的心 没关系 #
# Like the one in me, that's okay #
# 看看你有多厉害 握紧你的拳头 我们开始吧! #
# Let's see how you do it, put up your dukes, let's get down to it! #
# 放马过来 #
# Hit me with your best shot #
# 尽管放马过来吧 #
# Why don't you hit me with your best shot #
# 放马过来 #
# Hit me with your best shot #
# 开火吧 #
# Fire away #
《那一定是爱》  - 罗克赛特乐队
It Must Have Been Love - Roxette
# 那一定是爱 #
# It must have been Love #
# 但已经结束了 #
# But it's over now #
# 但已经彻底结束了 #
# But it's over right now #
兄弟姐妹们 这就是吸食大麻副作用
The negative side effects of medical marijuana, folks.
你被...
You are...
踢出局了!
Cut off!
磕多了药瞎捣乱 我们来看看下一个主题是什么吧
Stoney baloney. Let's check out our next category.
只要符合主题 任何歌都可以吗?
So, we just pick any song that works?
- 是的 任何歌  - 然后上去唱就行? 好的
- Yeah, any song.  - And you just go with it? Nice.
我们下一个主题是...
And our next category is...
- 跟性爱有关的歌  - 性爱?
- Songs about sex.  - Sex?
《禁忌游戏》  - 蕾哈娜 & 布兰妮・斯皮尔斯
S&M - Rihanna & Britney Spears
# 呐 呐 呐 来吧 #
# Na na na Come on #
# 呐 呐 呐 呐 呐 来吧 来吧 来吧 #
# Na na na na na. Come on, come on, come on #
# 或许我太放荡 但我的确很在行 #
# 'Cause I may be bad. But I'm perfectly good at it #
# 我不介意野战 我迷恋那野性的味道 #
# Sex in the air, I don't care I love the smell of it #
# 粗粝的器具可能让我伤痕累累 #
# Sticks and stones may break my bones #
# 但铁链和皮鞭让我欲罢不能 #
# But chains and whips excite me #
# 或许我太放荡 但我的确很在行 #
# 'Cause I may be bad. But I'm perfectly good at it #
《谈性说爱》  - 胡椒盐合唱团
Let's Talk about Sex - Salt N Pepa
# 来做爱吧 宝贝 来聊聊你和我 #
# Sex, baby. Let's talk about you and me #
# 来聊聊好的坏的 一切都有可能 #
# Let's talk about all the good things and the bad things that may be #
# 谈谈性说说爱 #
# Let's talk about sex #
# 谈谈性说说爱 来吧 来吧 #
# Let's talk about sex. A ittle bit, a Iittle bit #
# 谈谈性说说爱 宝贝 #
# Let's talk about sex, baby #
《我要和你做爱》  - 大人小孩双拍档
I'll Make Love To You - Boyz II Men
# 宝贝 一整夜 #
# Baby, all through the night #
# 我要和你做爱 听从你的意愿 #
# I'll make love to you. Like you want me to #
《仿如初恋》  - 外国佬乐队
Feels Like The First Time - Foreigner
# 我想是你的柔情似水 #
# And I guess it's just the woman in you #
# 唤醒了我内心的渴望 #
# That brings out the man in me #
# 我情难自禁 #
# I know I can't help myself #
# 你是我的全世界 #
# You're all in the world to me #
# 彷如初恋般心动 #
# It feels like the first time #
# 彷如初恋般浪漫 #
# It feels like the very first time #
# 彷如初恋般美妙 #
# It feels like the first time #
《不用怀疑》  - 黑街合唱团
No Diggity - Blackstreet
# 安静下来 迷失在黑街中 这帮兄弟找上我 有新玩意 #
# It's going down, fade to Blackstreet. The homies got RB, collab' creations #
# 不用说 大家像未成年一样嗨 我也来者不拒 绝不扫兴 #
# Bump like acne, no doubt I put it down, never slouch #
# 只要我钱够多 女人自会臣服于我 #
# As long as my credit can vouch a dog couldn't catch me straight up #
# 我要出手 谁敢拦我 我的魅力让这群美女无法自拔 #
# Tell me who can stop when Dre makin' moves attracting honeys like a magnet #
# 老练的腔调让她们高潮迭起 #
# Giving 'em eargasms with my mellow accent #
# 和我的黑街合唱团兄弟以及泰迪 #
# Still moving this flavor With the homies Blackstreet and Teddy #
# 他原是电臀高手 #
# The original rump shakers #
接着唱啊
Keep going.
# 小妞快来 天呐 #
# Shorty get down, good Lord #
# 宝贝 你让他们都疯狂 #
# Baby got 'em open all over town #
# 老实说 她从不跟人鬼混 #
# Strictly biz, she don't play around #
# 只是到处留情 如鱼得水 #
# Cover much ground, got game by the pound #
# 挣票子是她的拿手好戏 #
# Getting paid is her forte #
# 每天如此 完全就是感情浪子 #
# Each and every day, true player way #
# 我却总忘不了她 #
# I can't get her out of my mind #
不错啊
Okay.
# 我一直惦记着她 #
# I think about the girl all the time #
# 我喜欢这样的你 不用怀疑 #
# I like the way you work it, no diggity #
# 让我销魂一夜 宝贝 #
# I got to bag it up, baby #
# 我喜欢这样的你 不用怀疑 #
# I like the way you work it. No diggity #
# 让我销魂一夜 宝贝 #
# I got to bag it up, baby #
# 我喜欢这样的你 不用怀疑 #
# I like the way you work it. No diggity #
# 让我销魂一夜 宝贝 #
# I got to bag it up, baby #
# 我喜欢这样的你 不用怀疑 #
# I like the way you work it, no diggity #
# 让我销魂一夜 宝贝 #
# I got to bag it up, baby #
# 我喜欢这样的你 不用怀疑 #
# I like the way you work it, no diggity #
# 让我销魂一夜 宝贝 #
# I got to bag it up, baby #
# 我喜欢这样的你 不用怀疑 #
# I like the way you work it, no diggity #
# 让我销魂一夜 # 我们唱完了
# I got to bag it up # We out
我是说 不客气
I mean, you're welcome.
有一个严重的打击 女士们
It's a tough blow, ladies.
歌词要以"it"开头 但你们唱的是"it's"
The word you needed to match was "it." And you sang, "it's."
- 你们...  - 出局了!
- You are...  - Cut off!
- 当真吗?  - 刺儿头小子赢了
- Are you serious?  - The Trebles win!
贝卡 对不起 你们输了
Beca, I'm sorry. You lost.
我从没听说还有这规定! 女孩们 算了 回来吧
I've never heard that rule! Ladies, ladies, come on. Come back.
对不起
Sorry.
胜者为王啊
Money in the bank.
就等着欣赏我们赢得ICCA比赛吧
Enjoy watching us win the ICCAs.
在电视上 全区有线电视网
On the TV. On a regional cable affiliate.
在大家睡觉之前
Before everybody goes to bed tonight,
我要你们列下自己做过的所有错事
I need you to make a list of everything you did wrong.
我要煮了那个椰菜娃娃
I'm gonna melt that Cabbage Patch Kid.
嘿 大伙 我们刚才很棒 不是吗?
Hey, guys, what we just did was great, right?
别得意了 贝卡 我们还是输了
Calm your pits, Beca. We still lost.
没错 但那是即兴的 很了不起
Yeah, but it was spontaneous. It was awesome.
我们真的听了...
We were actually listening to...
好了 大家 伸出手
Okay, everybody, hands in.
我数后"啊"
"Ah" on my count.
- 数到三还是数完三?  - 数到三
- On three or after three?  - On three.
- 数完三  - 一 二 三
- After three.  - One, two, three.
我们不是这么做的
That's not how we do it.
哦! 我们怎么连这都搞不清呢?
Oh! Why can't we figure this out?
所以 我就找到和弦行进相同的歌曲
So, I just find songs that have the same chord progressions
然后把它们合在一起做了个小调
and create a track that blends them together.
嗯 这是新的低音线
So, like, this is the new bass line,
而这是配和的强拍
and this is matching up downbeats.
哦 我说话太大声了
Oh, I'm talking really loud.
歌是我唱的
That's me singing.
很不错
This is really good.
现在是我大喊大叫了 是吧?
Now I'm the one yelling, right?
太棒了 贝卡
That is amazing, Beca.
谢谢
Thanks.
话说 我把这个带来了
So, I brought this over,
因为我想看你把电影结尾看完
because I wanna watch you watch the end of this movie.
然后我也死而无憾了
And then I can die a hero.
你还真的从不把自己当外人 是吗?
You have a habit of making yourself at home, did you know that?
没错
Yeah.
嗯...
Hmm...
好吧
Okay.
早餐俱乐部 1985年的电影
The Breakfast Club. 1985.
史上最棒的电影结局
Greatest ending to any movie ever.
这歌让"头脑简单乐团"在美国走红
This song launched Simple Minds in the US.
本来是让比利 爱多尔演唱的 但他拒绝了
Could have been a Billy Idol song, but he turned it down.
白痴
Idiot.
很好的归纳了电影 非常的优美哀伤
Perfectly sums up the movie. It's equally beautiful and sad.
很迷人啊
That is fascinating.
没错吧?
Right?
告诉我 贾德・尼尔森早餐吃的什么?
Tell me, what does Judd Nelson eat for breakfast?
哦 这个 像所有被误解的反叛者一样 他以虚伪为食
Oh, well, like all misunderstood rebels, he feeds on hypocrisy.
没错
Sure.
还有黑咖啡来提神
And black coffee to help with his morning dumps.
你真傻
You're an idiot.
是真的 我肚子里全是趣闻
It's true. I'm full of fun facts.
是不是有趣 你应该让别人来说
You should let other people tell you they're fun.
和一个运动员
And an athlete.
一个神经病
And a basket case.
一个公主
A princess.
和一个罪犯
And a criminal.
这回答了你的问题了吗?
Does that answer your question?
你诚挚的 早餐俱乐部
Sincerely yours, the Breakfast Club.
你又没看到结尾
You're missing the ending.
抱歉
Sorry.
很不错 我敢说开头也...
It's good. I'm sure the beginning is...
白人女孩回来了
The white girl is back.
我该走了
And I'm out.
很高兴见到你 金凯米
Always a pleasure, Kimmy Jin.
那么... 抱歉 借过
So... Excuse me. Excuse me.
你们说要多做有氧运动 我应该当回事的
I should have taken that cardio tip more seriously.
你做了多少有氧运动?
How much have you done?
你看也看出来了
You just saw it.
克洛伊 你必须唱好最后那个音
Chloe, you gotta be able to hit that last note.
我不行 那不可能的
I can't. It's impossible.
而这是因为我的 我的小结
And it's because of my, my nodes.
- 她的小结  - 她的小结
- Her nodes. - Her nodes.
好吧 如果你唱不了 那就得找其他人独唱
Well, if you can't do it, then someone else needs to solo.
我觉得贝卡可以替我独唱
I think Beca should take my solo.
是的 贝卡会很棒
Yeah, Beca would be excellent.
但是 或许还有其他人也一样棒
But also, someone else might be equally as excellent.
- 没错  - 而她们可能很害羞
- It's true.  - And they might be shy
不好意思站出来说她想独唱
and not wanna come forward and say they wanted a solo.
这样啊 既然贝卡不想独唱 那么...
Well, Beca doesn't want a solo, so...
如果可以让我
I would be happy to do it
选首新歌做些调整 我很乐意独唱
if I got to pick a new song and do an arrangement.
我们这儿可不是那么安排的
Well, that's not how we run things here.
奥布里 或许贝卡说得有道理 或许我们该尝试新东西
Aubrey, maybe Beca has a point. Maybe we could try something new.
什么?
A-ca-scuse me?
你可以唱"舞力无限" 不要再让我听到类似的话
You can sing Turn the Beat Around and that's the last I wanna hear of this.
那首歌很乏味 我们靠它不会赢的
That song is tired. We're not gonna win with it.
如果我们从不同流派找选取歌曲
If we pull samples from different genres
把它们重新混音 我们可以做出...
and layer them together, we could make some...
够了 显然你没懂什么意思 那我就说给你听
Okay, let me explain something to you because you still don't seem to get it.
我们的目标是进入决赛 而那三首歌会让我们进入
Our goal is to get back to the finals and these songs will get us there.
所以 抱歉我不想听一个叛逆女孩荒谬的自由节拍理论
So, excuse me if I don't take advice from some alt-girl with her mad lib beats,
因为她从没有参加过比赛
because she's never even been in competition.
听清楚了吗?
Have I made myself clear?
非常清楚 我不独唱了
Crystal. I won't solo.
好吧
Fine.
- 胖艾米  - 是 长官?
- Fat Amy?  - Yes, sir?
你来独唱
You'll solo.
耶! 棒
Yes! Yes.
地区赛当天
女士们 先生们 欢迎大家
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen.
2012东南地区地区赛正式开幕
The 2012 southeastern regional competition has officially begun.
是的 我是盖尔・艾伯纳西・马凯德
Yes, I'm Gail Abernathy McCadd,
我右边的同事是无伴奏演唱者约翰・史密斯
and to my right is fellow a cappella alum John Smith
这是在卡罗莱纳大学进行现场直播
and we are live from Carolina University.
这是无伴奏合唱比赛的新赛季
It's a new season for a cappella.
所有单靠嘴巴创作音乐的年轻人
The regionals begin the long road to Lincoln Center
都希望有朝一日在林肯中心功成名就
where all of these youngsters hope to one day win a trophy
漫漫长路从地区赛开始
by making music with their mouths.
用袜子木偶合唱? 天才啊
A cappella out of sock puppets? Genius.
没错 看那个戴白袜子的黑人
Yeah, look at the black one with the white sock.
真是效果显著啊
It's making a statement.
这没有技术含量 学习他们只会让你们更糟
There's no craft there. Watching them will make you worse.
至少他们与众不同
At least they're different.
袜偶贝拉合唱团 再一次证明了
And the Sockappellas, once again proving
他们从高中后就没有起色了
that it doesn't get better for everyone after high school.
我们鼓掌吗?
Do we clap?
不 不鼓掌 从不
No, we don't. Never.
伸出手
Hands in.
记住 数到三"啊"
Remember, "ah" on three.
一 二...
One, two...
慢着 你之前说...
Wait, you said we'd...
抱歉
I'm sorry.
没事 会没事的 没事
It's okay, it's gonna be okay. Okay.
让我们欢迎巴顿贝拉合唱团!
Let's give it up for the Barden Bellas!
哇哦
Wow.
这可不是我们熟知的面容娇嫩又性感的贝拉阵容啊
This does not look like the fresh-faced nubile Bellas that we have come to know.
是我的问题还是那些裙子真的过时了?
Is it me or are those skirts just not working anymore?
你越说越离谱啊 约翰
You're walking the line, John.
很惊喜看到贝拉组内有了混搭
It's a nice surprise to see the Bellas mixing it up.
非常新鲜 但是不太入眼啊
It's refreshing, yet displeasing to the eye.
一 二 三 四
One, two, three, four.
巴顿贝拉合唱团带来的
The Barden Bellas bringing back
正是去年决赛时演唱的曲目
the same song they sang at last year's finals.
所有目光都会聚焦在大四的奥布里 柏森身上
And all eyes will be on senior Aubrey Posen.
她随时可能喷吐出些饼干
She could toss some cookies at any moment.
她顺利完成了 观众们 没有饼干喷出
And she makes it through, folks. No cookie toss.
约翰 看来巴顿贝拉合唱团近期是不会有什么新的编排了
John, a change of pace could not come soon enough here for the Barden Bellas.
这个赛季没有开个好头啊
This is not a great way to start their season.
没错 这首歌听得观众耳朵都长茧子了
Yeah, this number is like an elephant dart to the public's face.
哦 耶!
Oh, yeah!
好
Yes.
真棒 胖艾米
Yeah, Fat Amy.
嘣!
Boo!
巴顿贝拉合唱团可以因这首歌名留史册了 约翰
The Barden Bellas went deep into the archive for that song, John.
我还记得和我的合唱团一起唱这首歌呢
I remember singing it with my own a cappella group.
是什么合唱团啊 盖尔?
And what group was that, Gail?
吟游诗人合唱团 约翰
The Minstrel Cycles, John.
呃 名字真难听啊
Well, that's an unfortunate name.
谢谢 非常精彩
Thank you. Really incredible.
巴顿贝拉合唱团 谢谢
The Barden Bellas. Thank you.
非常棒
That was great.
太惊艳了
Amazing.
我说 巴顿大学真是不一般啊
You know, there must be something in the water over there at Barden University,
因为下一个组合同样来自巴顿大学
'cause this next group is also from Barden.
女士们先生们 巴顿大学的刺儿头小子合唱团
Ladies and gentlemen, the Barden University Treblemakers.
又来了 巴顿刺儿头小子合唱团 他们已经在去林肯中心的路上了 哈?
Here we go, the Barden Treblemakers. They're on the trail for Lincoln Center, huh?
绝对的 一直都是 盖尔
Absolutely, they always are, Gail.
我的最爱 也是大家的最爱
My favorite, and everyone's favorite.
我的备注上说他们的负责人邦博尔・艾伦
Now it says here in my notes that their front man Bumper Allen
最近发布了他自己的运动凉鞋系列啊
has recently released his own line of sports sandals.
嘘!
Shh!
天哪 合唱团的坏男孩们真是变得更坏了
Boy, the bad boys of a cappella have just gotten badder.
哇呜! 说得没错 约翰
Whoo! That's right, John.
为此我得去市里做做美容了
I'm gonna have to excuse myself to freshen up the downtown.
我能帮忙吗?
Can I help?
女士们先生们 我们期待已久的时刻到了
Ladies and gentlemen, the moment we've all been waiting for.
今晚的地区赛结果
The results of tonight's regional competition.
第三名 袜偶贝拉合唱团!
In third place, the Sockappellas!
- 耶 算你走运  - 第二名
- Yeah, lucky you.  - In second place,
进入到今年半决赛的 巴顿贝拉合唱团
and advancing to this year's semi-finals, the Barden Bellas.
耶
Yeah.
真棒!
Yes!
太赞了
Awesome.
哦 不错 不错
Oh, nice. Nice.
嘿 哼!
Hey, ugh!
而今晚地区赛的冠军
And the winner of tonight's regional competition,
女士们先生们 正是卫冕冠军
defending their crown, ladies and gentlemen,
巴顿大学的刺儿头小子合唱团!
the Barden University Treblemakers!
干得不错 刺儿头小子
Way to go, Trebles.
爽! 赞!
Yes! Yes!
就是这样!
That's right!
我想在胸上签名 没错! 我想签...
I'm willing to sign breasts. Yes! I'm willing to sign...
哦 看看是谁啊 老家伙们
Oh, look who it is. Old dudes.
找点事做吧
Get a life.
像音爆一样
Sonic boom.
虽然我们已经毕业几年了
Just 'cause we graduated a few years ago,
但并不意味着我们不能重现舌尖上的魔法 好吗?
doesn't mean we can't still get off performing our oral magic, all right?
舌尖上的魔法?
Oral magic?
哦 哦 伙计 伙计
Whoa, whoa, whoa, buddy, buddy.
你是想干我认为你要干的事吗?
Are you looking for what I think you're looking for?
没错 打架? 你是想打架吗?
Yeah, a fight? You looking for a fight?
拜托 帮忙 说你们是想打架的
Please, please. Please say you're looking for a fight.
拜托说你们是想打架
Please, please say you're looking for a fight.
没错! 我来打
Yes! I will fight.
我本来是会跟他打的
I would fight him,
但是跳舞的时候我拉伤了四肢
but I tore a quad within the midst of the dance...
- 嘿 甘地 嘿 你  - 我们到底要不要打?
- Hey, Gandhi. Hey, you.  - Are we doing this or what?
- 打我  - 什么?
- Hit me.  - What?
让我们开战吧!
Let's get it on!
别啊
Mmm-mmm.
我曾经同时斗过鳄鱼和野狗
I've wrestled crocodiles and dingoes simultaneously.
- 过来!  - 你为什么想让我打你?
- Come here!  - Why do you want me to hit you?
我不想动手
I don't wanna do that.
我需要一些感觉 尽力打我吧
I need to feel something. Hit me as hard as you can.
重重地打 拿着这个 拿着 用这个打我
Hit me hard. Take this. Take this. I want you to hit me with it.
我就过去一下... 过去看看他们
I'm just gonna... I'm just gonna check on them.
海怪被释放出来了 领教胖艾米的力量吧!
The kraken has been unleashed. Feel the Fat Amy force!
嘿
Hey.
哦 天哪 哦 上帝
Oh, my God. Oh, my gosh.
哦!
Oh!
那感觉真奇妙!
That's fantastic!
- 艾米 别 艾米!  - 感受强大的力量吧
- Amy, don't. Amy!  - Feel the fat power.
胖艾米! 踢我的蛋蛋
Fat Amy! Kick me in the balls!
艾米!
Amy!
快把这个利器给我 我要插进他屁股里!
Give me the sharp weapon, I wanna put it up his butt!
哦! 不要手软啊
Ooh! Cherry on top.
你从哪边跑?
Which way are you running?
- 这边 这边  - 好
- This way. This way.  - All right.
干得漂亮
Beautiful.
艾米!
Amy!
直线逃跑
Vertical running.
我要直线逃跑
I'm vertical running.
嘿 "百万宝贝"里的希拉里斯万克
Hey, Hilary Swank from Million Dollar Baby.
嘿 你只说"嘿 百万宝贝"就行了
Hey, you know you just have to say, "Hey, Million Dollar Baby."
没必要指明是哪个女演员
You don't have to reference the specific actress.
该死的 监狱改变了你
Damn. Prison changed you.
谢谢你把我保释出来
Thanks for bailing me out.
保释你的不是我
Well, I didn't.
你叫了我爸爸?
You called my dad?
我知道你不想 但是他们把你铐上了哎 贝卡
I know, I know, but they were putting you in handcuffs, Bec.
看起来很严重
It looked pretty serious.
这也不表示你可以告诉我爸爸
That doesn't mean you call my dad.
那我还能叫谁呢? 好了 你为什么要冲我喊啊?
Who else was I gonna call? Okay, why are you yelling at me?
就我一个人留下来等你
I'm the only one here.
我又没让你留下来
I didn't ask you to be.
我只是想帮你
I was just trying to help you.
我不需要你的帮助 你又不是我男朋友
I don't need your help, you're not my boyfriend.
明白了
Got it.
- 爸爸 这没什么  - 是吗 这很严重
- Dad, it's not a big deal.  - Yeah, it's a big deal.
我半夜接到电话
I get a call in the middle of the night
说我女儿因为毁坏公物被捕了
saying my daughter's been arrested for destruction of property.
这是误会 我在保护我的朋友
It was a misunderstanding and I was protecting my friends.
我在让自己融入环境 创造回忆
I was putting myself out there. Making memories.
如果你以为这样的闹剧过后 我还会供你去洛杉矶
If you think I'm paying for you to go to L.A. after a stunt like this,
你就错了 上车
I'm not. Get in the car.
你难道都不听我解释吗?
You're not even gonna hear what I have to say about this?
不 今晚不听 上车吧
No, not tonight. Just get in.
嘿!
Hey!
监狱怎么样啊?
What up, Shawshank?
给自己找个马子了吗?
Did you get yourself a bitch?
他们用水管喷你了吗?
Did they spray you with a hose?
我在县监狱被喷过
I did a turn at County.
你们在等我?
You guys waited up for me?
我们当然要等你了
Of course we waited up for you.
她们在这儿好几个小时了 非常不方便 贝卡
They've been here for hours. It's a real inconvenience, Beca.
贝卡 很高兴你在这儿
Beca, I'm glad you're here.
我要开一次紧急贝拉组会
I'm calling an emergency Bella meeting.
不是吧
No.
- 首先...  - 好吧
- First up...  - Yes.
我们的记分表显示袜偶贝拉合唱团差点就赢我们了
Our score sheet revealed that the Sockappellas almost beat us.
还有胖艾米 比赛时就按照彩排来 不要随意发挥 好吗?
And Fat Amy, you need to do it exactly how we rehearsed it, okay?
没有惊喜
No surprises.
我们应该冒冒险 这样还不够好
We should be taking risks. It's not enough to be good,
我们需要释放自己 与众不同
we need to put ourselves out there, be different.
贝卡说得对 刺儿头小子从不唱一样的歌
Beca's right. The Trebles never sing the same song twice.
观众喜欢刺儿头小子 他们在忍受我们
The audience love the Trebles, they tolerate us.
我们可以让合唱团改头换面 如果我们...
We could change the face of a cappella if we...
哦 天哪 这听起来太怪异了 我这是怎么了?
Oh, my God, that sounded so queerballs. What's happening to me?
让我给你看我一直在筹备的改编
Let me show you this arrangement I've been working on.
我不知道你还喜欢这个
I didn't know you were into this stuff.
嗯
Yeah.
好了 我有决定权 而我说我们要专注练习计划好的歌单
Okay, I have the pitch pipe, and I say that we focus on the set list as planned.
从现在起 没有时间再浪费在爱好
From now on, there will be no more wasting time with work
学校 男朋友 或者同伴上了
or school or boyfriends or partners.
抱歉 辛西娅・罗丝
Sorry, Cynthia Rose.
但是奥布里 这个真的很酷 我是说...
But Aubrey, this stuff is pretty cool. I mean...
好了 明天彩排 八点整
Okay. Rehearsal tomorrow, 8:00 a.m. sharp.
嘿!
Hey!
这是我的作品! 你现在在放我的歌曲!
This is my track! You're playing my song right now!
真是太了不起了! 你喜欢吗?
That is awesome! You like it?
你放在广播上了! 太惊奇了!
You put it on the radio! That is amazing!
让人受不了的节奏
It's a sick beat.
没错 我一直觉得她的节奏挺让人受不了的
Yeah, I always thought her beats were pretty sick.
嘿 贝卡 听着 春假的时候 我想你来值夜班
Hey, Becky, listen, spring break, I want you to take the night shift.
放你的音乐
Play your music.
这首歌 车库摇滚DJ的版本非常出色 但是你的呢? 更好
The DJ at the Garage does a brilliant version of this, but yours? It's better.
是的 没错
Yeah, it is.
我今晚要听她的 我觉得你应该... 你也应该来
I'm gonna listen to her tonight. I think you should... you should come with.
我有事情
I have a thing.
空姐训练?
Flight attendant training?
是巴顿贝拉合唱团 我今晚有半决赛
It's Barden Bellas. I have the semi-finals tonight.
真的? 我无法想象你会无伴奏合唱
Really? I did not have you pegged as an a cappella girl.
那是因为你没有我了解贝卡
That's 'cause you don't know Becky like I do.
晚上见
See you tonight.
没事 你们群妞儿别担心 我来处理
Okay, don't you flat-butts worry, I got this.
我只要加下油就行了
I'm just gonna pump and dump.
我不管你说什么
I don't care what you say.
西斯科的现场 我所看过的最好的表演
Sisqo live, best performance ever, I've ever seen.
"皮带歌"不是他唯一的成功作
"Thong Song" isn't his only hit. Yeah.
不是吗? 这是认真的
All right? That's serious.
哟 邦博尔 那不是胖艾米吗?
Yo, Bump, is that Fat Amy?
唐纳德 减速! 慢点!
Donald, slow down! Slow down!
耶! 很好!
Yeah! All right!
嘿 艾米? 搞破坏咯!
Hey, Amy? Sabotage!
我被击中了
I've been shot.
我刚被击中了! 救命啊
I've just been shot! Help me.
胖艾米!
Fat Amy!
他们击中了艾米!
They shot Amy!
有我呢 有我呢
I've got you. I've got you.
别 不用 我在说话 我还能说话... 我坐起来了
No, no, no. I'm talking, I'm talking... I'm sitting up.
- 好了 没事了  - 不需要这样
- All right. Cool.  - There's no need for that.
不用人工呼吸
No mouth to mouth.
哦 靠 邦博尔冲我扔了一个超大的玉米煎饼
Oh, shit. Bumper threw a big-ass burrito at me.
我要杀了他 我发誓 我要把他打成奶油蛋糕
I'm gonna kill him, I swear. I'm gonna finish him like a cheesecake.
你这里还有一点东西
You've got yourself a little something there.
别管了 它能一直点燃我的恨意
Just leave it. It fuels my hate fire.
哦 天呐
Oh, my God.
那是... 是...
It's a... It's...
哦
Oh.
搞什么?
What the hell?
呃... 那真是很酷 实际上 我想我们没油了
Um... It's pretty cool, actually. I think we're just running out of gas.
不 不可能 你刚刚才加满的
No, that can't be. You just filled the tank.
是的 我加了
Yeah, I did.
但是 或许我没加 因为我被飞来的墨西哥快餐打中了
And, yet, maybe I didn't, because I got hit by flying Mexican food.
我们没油了
And we're out.
说什么?
A-ca-scuse me?
不是吧
A-ca-believe it.
伙计 我们该怎么办?
Man, what are we gonna do?
也许 我们可以打电话给...
Maybe we could call...
克洛伊 提都别提 你怎么敢?
No, don't even say it, Chloe. How dare you?
别啊 这想法其实挺好的 我有邦博尔的号码
Oh, no, actually that is a really good idea. I've got Bumper's number.
你为什么会有邦博尔的号码?
Why do you have Bumper's number?
贝拉队员们
So, Bellas,
多无聊的雌性团体 你们准备好今晚被我们打败了吗?
what boring, estrogen-filled set have you prepared for us this evening?
什么?
Excuse me?
不过你们这群家伙到时会输得很惨
But you guys are gonna get pitch-slapped so hard
再也抬不起头来
your man boobs are gonna concave.
还有9英里
Nine miles, guys.
相当不错啊
That's pretty good.
我放火时会觉得开心
I set fires to feel joy.
真可爱
That's adorable.
贝拉 5分钟后上场
Five minutes, Bellas.
- 他哪儿来的?  - 嘘!
- Where did he come from?  - Shh!
完了 我们不可能打败脚注合唱团和刺儿头小子的
It's over. There's no way we can beat the Footnotes and the Trebles.
哇! 这个小个子真能唱
Whoo! That little peanut can sing.
真的不错 不过 盖尔 在我听来 他好像还没发育完全
He really can. It sounds to me, though, Gail, like his boys haven't dropped yet,
你懂我意思的
if you know what I mean.
如果你指他的下体 我懂 约翰 真的懂
If you mean his testicles, then I do, John. I do. I really do.
过来 过来
A-ca-huddle, now.
只有前两名能进入决赛 我们必须要打败他们其中一个
The top two teams go to the finals, so we just have to beat one of them.
只要我们完完全全按照排练的表演 就能成功 好吗? 完完全全
And if we do it exactly how we rehearsed it, we will get there, okay? Exactly.
伸出手
Hands in.
数到三时 还是数完三之后?
On three or after three?
算了 上吧
Screw it. Let's just do it.
掌声有请出巴顿贝拉合唱团!
Put your hands together for the Barden Bellas!
好的 贝拉要出场了
Okay, the Bellas are coming out.
本次大赛中的第二步...
Another step in this competition and...
一 二 三 四...
One, two, three, four...
又来了
Here we go again.
这个曲目编排 她们似乎想要一路坚持到底了
Looks like they're sticking with what they know.
她们今晚在台上有点紧张啊
A little tension on the stage tonight.
不过有了些进攻性
Claws are out.
这只是大学生间友好的娱乐而已
This is just friendly collegiate fun.
比赛十分激烈 但我们在此也享受到了美好时光
It's a tough competition, but we're all here to have a good time.
没错 约翰 不过一个错误就能困扰你一辈子
That's right, John. But a mistake can haunt you for the rest of your life
还能影响到你的后辈
and affect your children.
到底怎么回事 贝卡? 你是想毁了我们吗?
What the hell, Beca? Were you trying to screw us up?
你当真吗?
Are you serious?
简单申明 这并不是贝卡的独唱秀
Newsflash. This isn't the Beca show.
好吧 很抱歉搅乱了你的演出
Okay, I'm sorry that I messed you up,
但你可能没注意到吧 我们演唱的时候 大家都快睡着了
but in case you hadn't noticed, everybody pretty much dozed off during our set.
不用你来决定我们该唱什么 什么时候该唱
It's not your job to decide what we do and when we do it.
你怎么不问问其他组员对你的即兴表演有什么感想?
Why don't you ask the rest of the group how they felt about your little improvisation?
艾米?
Amy?
很棒 但的确让我们有点小惊讶
It was cool. But it did take us a little bit by surprise.
是非常惊讶
Yeah, a lot by surprise.
一点点
A little.
- 我早告诉过你 她不适合阿卡贝拉  - 奥布里 别说了
- I told you she wasn't a Bella.  - Aubrey, don't.
不用 没事的 你不用假装
No, that's okay. You don't have to pretend
自己在这组里有发言权 好吗?
you're allowed to have a say in the group, right?
你的态度真恶劣 我实在是看不惯你
Your attitude sucks. You're a grade-A pain in my ass,
我就知道你跟杰西有一腿
and I know you're hooking up with Jesse.
奥布里 冷静 我发誓 我们可是清白得很
Whoa. Whoa. Aubrey, calm down. We're not hooking up, I swear.
天啊! 太棒了! 就知道这时你肯定会出现
Jesus Christ! That's perfect. Of course you're here right now.
我不需要你的帮忙 好吗? 你能靠边站吗?
I don't need your help, okay? Can you back off?
刺儿头小子 该上场了
Trebles. Time to bring the pain.
如果这就是我努力的结局...
If this is what I get for trying...
贝卡? 贝卡 等等
Beca? Beca, wait.
奥布里 其实表演效果也很好
Aubrey, it actually went really well.
够了 克洛伊!
Chloe, stop!
抱歉 噢 天啊 好吧
Excuse me. Oh, my God. Okay.
贝卡? 贝卡 等等
Beca? Beca, wait.
我的孩子是JFK高中的荣誉学生
刺儿头小子合唱团今晚拔得头筹
And the Treblemakers seal the deal tonight.
很不幸 巴顿的另一支合唱团 贝拉合唱团 不幸出局
Unfortunately, Barden's other group, the Bellas, do not advance,
毕业班的奥布里・柏森失去了一洗去年呕吐门的机会
and senior Aubrey Posen loses her chance to redeem herself from last year's Pukegate.
春假快乐
Happy spring break.
谢谢
Thanks.
用最简单的词 用最方便的定义
In the simplest terms, in the most convenient definitions.
但我们才发现 我们分别是一个书呆子
But what we found out is that each one of us is a brain.
和一个运动员
And an athlete.
一个神经病
And a basket case.
一个公主
A princess.
和一个罪犯
And a criminal.
这回答了你的问题了吗?
Does that answer your question?
你诚挚的 早餐俱乐部
Sincerely yours, the Breakfast Club.
噢 天啊
Oh, my God.
好了
Okay.
我们是全国大学生无伴奏演唱协会的
We are from the Collegiate A Cappella Association.
我们注意到 你并不是大学生
It has come to our attention that you are not in college.
这位是你母亲吗?
Is this your mother?
我是奥布里・柏森
This is Aubrey Posen.
是 谢谢你 先生
Yes, thank you, sir.
很期待在林肯中心再次与您会面
I look forward to seeing you again at Lincoln Center.
耶!
Yes!
奥布里?
Aubrey?
我全跟了 各位
I'm all in, bitches.
好了 上帝终于垂青我们了 又给了我们一次机会
Okay. The a-ca-gods have looked down on us and they have given us a second chance.
太好了!
Shalom!
我短信通知贝卡了
I texted Beca.
你怎么了?
You did what?
有她在 我们更强
She makes us better.
克洛伊 你不该有这种想法的
That's not an opinion for you to have, Chloe.
为什么? 因为你不是这样想的?
Why? Because it's not yours?
你要知道 你也不是永远都对
You're not always right, you know.
没有她 我们也一样能赢
We will win without her.
杰西 我知道你在里面 我闻到爆米花味了
Jesse, I know you're in there. I can smell popcorn.
杰西 拜托 开门吧
Jesse, come on. Open up.
嘿 我给你打了电话 还发了好多信息
Hey. I tried to call you. I left you a bunch of messages.
嗯 我收到了
Yeah, I got them.
很抱歉之前和你吵架
I'm sorry that we fought.
我当时太生气了 反应过度了 我只是...
I was mad and I overreacted and I'm just...
奥布里让我有些情绪失控
Aubrey makes me crazy.
真的吗?
Seriously?
你以为我是因为你对我吼 所以才生气的?
You think I'm mad because you yelled at me?
不 我知道...
No, I know...
你根本不知道 你以为自己知道 但你不知道
No, you don't. You think you know, but you don't.
只要有人想关心你 你就拒他们于千里之外 为什么?
You push away anyone who could possibly care about you. Why is that?
我不知道
I don't know.
那你最好去搞清楚 因为我已经受够了...
Well, you better figure it out because I'm done with...
管这算什么关系呢
whatever this is.
- 杰西...  - 我受够了
- Jesse...  - I'm done.
女人啊
Women.
是啊
Yeah.
好了 停
Okay, stop.
我们这是怎么了?
What is happening to us?
克洛伊 你的声音听起来好像是一天抽三包烟似的
Chloe, you sound like you smoke three packs a day.
斯蒂西 你的舞蹈方面落后太多了
Stacie, you are so behind on choreography.
还有杰西卡和艾什莉 你们好像有一年没训练过了
And Jessica and Ashley, it is like you haven't been here all year long.
奥布里 说真的吗?
Aubrey, really?
我们一直在这里训练
We've literally been here the whole time.
奥布里让我们休息一下吧
Aubrey, please, just give us a break.
人不到齐 感觉好像都变了
It's kind of not the same without everyone here.
我们需要贝卡
We need Beca.
如果奥布里少管一些 也许会好些
Maybe if Aubrey loosened the reins a little bit.
好了 闭嘴 克洛伊!
Okay, shut it, Chloe!
抱歉 我太粗鲁了
Oh, I'm sorry. That was rude.
克洛伊 你能不要再用屁股想问题了吗? 脑子不在那里
Chloe, could you please get your head out of your ass? It's not a hat.
真尴尬
A-ca-awkward.
再来一次
Again.
我自己才最惊讶 但我真的很喜欢那些女孩
No one was more surprised than me, but I really liked those girls.
你觉得只要退出就可以了吗?
And you thought quitting was the answer?
真的吗? 你好意思这么说我?
Seriously? You can say that to me?
拜托 贝卡 这样说可不公平
Oh, come on, Bec, that's so unfair.
听着 你妈妈和我 我们就是不适合了
Look, your mom and I, we didn't work.
但我一直努力想缓和我们之间的关系
But I tried so hard to make things right between us.
而你 你只是一味地疏远我
But you, you just shut me out.
对 我对所有人都疏远 不是针对你
Yeah, well, I shut everybody out. Don't take it personally.
只是这样更容易
It's just easier.
这样也真的会很孤单
It's also really lonely.
我该怎么办?
What do I do?
那就看你自己了
Well, that's up to you.
刺儿头小子们 听着!
Trebles, listen up!
如果是贝拉进入决赛的消息 那我们已经知道了
If this is about the Bellas getting into the finals, we already know.
我才不关心那群蠢女人
I don't give a crap about those dumb bitches.
因为我要去开创音乐事业了
Because I'm being brought up to the musical big leagues.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
约翰梅尔透过助理 亲自请我
John Mayer just asked me, personally, through an assistant,
给他的新唱片做伴唱
to sing backup on his new CD.
我过几个小时 就要出发去洛杉矶了 所以现在得走了
I leave for Los Angeles in a few hours, so I gotta get going.
但是邦博尔 ICCA比赛怎么办? 这周末啊
But Bumper, what about the ICCAs? They're this weekend.
抱歉啦 伙计们 这种玩意我都赢腻了 我要走喽
Hmm. Sorry, buddies, but I won that shit like 100 times, so I'm out of here.
我要去买个无领皮夹克 或者买个飞行眼镜
Got a collarless leather jacket to buy. Maybe some aviators.
还有耳环 算不清啦
I might get an earring, I don't know.
洛杉矶啊 真兴奋啊 我的人生啊!
It's Los Angeles. This is exciting stuff. My life rules!
- 邦博尔是个混蛋 好吧 我就是骂出来了  - 嗯
- Bumper's a jerk. All right, I said it.  - Yeah.
- 不过我们得找人来代替这个混蛋了  - 嗯
- Well, he's a jerk that we need to replace.  - Yeah.
尽快
Pronto dente.
你知道吗 他自己假装粉丝给自己写信
You know he writes his own fan mail.
机会来了 你想要 就是你的了
Spot opened up, and it's yours if you want it.
只有一个条件 保证你不会表现得怪异
Just one condition. Promise me you won't get all weird.
我们只是一个歌唱团体 好吗?
We're just a group of guys singing a bunch of covers of songs, okay?
你要是表现得怪异 他们绝对不会让你待下去
If you get weird, they will definitely not let you stay.
好 只是我不知道怎么算是怪异
Deal. Although I don't know what you mean by weird.
明白了
Got it.
我在这儿支持了你这么多年 而你却这样对我...
I have been there for you for so many years, and all you do is treat me like...
好了 闭嘴! 各位!
All right, no, okay, just shut up! Everyone!
拜托 我当时加入 是因为我想和一群很酷的女孩在一起
Come on, I joined this group so I could hang out with a bunch of really cool chicks.
当然了 还因为我真的厌烦了我所有的男朋友
And also 'cause I was really sick of all my boyfriends
我需要逃离那一切
and I need to get away from that.
但这儿现在真的太糟了
But this is some serious horseshit.
什么味道? 到处都臭臭的
What's that smell? Stinks everywhere.
我不想再像老贝拉组员一样了
I don't wanna be like the old Bellas.
是 我喜欢我们现在的样子
Yeah, I wanna be how we are now.
我也是
Me, too.
我们应该听听贝卡的意见
We should have listened to Beca.
所以是我的错了?
Oh, so it's my fault?
我可没这么说
That's not what I'm saying.
不 你们都是这样想的 不是吗?
No, no, no, that's what you're all thinking, isn't it?
认为我是笨蛋 认为我眼中只有胜利
That I'm the jerk. I am the girl obsessed with winning.
奥布里 你控制欲太强了 那样会毁了我们
Aubrey, you're too controlling and it's gonna ruin all of us.
是吗 我要想失控 我也可以失控
You know what, I can lose control if I want to.
我也可以不管不顾 这次我不会抑制了
I can let go. This time I'm not gonna choke it down.
嗯?
Hmm?
来啊 继续啊! 这才哪到哪啊!
Come on, bring it! You can do better than that!
你就这样了吗?
That's all you got?
够了! 够了!
Enough! Enough!
我们本来可以夺冠的!
We could have been champions!
给我音笛 你个混蛋!
Give me the pitch pipe, you bitch!
给我!
Give it to me!
给我! 把它给我!
Give it to me! Give it to me!
别想!
Never!
我来保护你 保护你
I'll protect you. I'll protect you.
手给我拿开!
Hands off the goodies!
滚开 你们这群混蛋!
Move, you bitches!
各位!
Guys!
大家停手! 这是在干吗?
Guys, stop! What is going on?
没事 没事 这只是贝拉排演
Nothing. Nothing. This is a Bellas rehearsal.
我知道 我只是
I know. I just
想要说 我很抱歉
wanted to say that I'm sorry.
我之前的行为真的很不对
What I did was a really dick move
我不应该在没有问过大家的情况下 就即兴发挥
and I shouldn't have changed the set without asking you guys.
我当然也不该负气离开
And I definitely shouldn't have left.
让大家失望了 我真的很抱歉
I let you guys down and I'm really sorry.
还有...
And...
奥布里 如果你还接纳我 我想要回来
Aubrey, if you would have me, I want back in.
奥布里
Aubrey.
等等
Wait.
谢谢 不然就尴尬了
Thank you. That would have been embarrassing.
贝卡 我知道我对你一直很苛刻 对吧?
Beca, I know that I've been hard on you, okay?
我知道 我对这儿的所有人都很苛刻
I know that I have been hard on everyone here.
但都是我父亲教出来的
But I am my father's daughter.
他总是说 "如果起初你就没有成功
And he always said, "If at first you don't succeed,
那就收拾铺盖走人吧"
pack your bags."
天啊 真是疯了
Jesus. That's really crazy.
我懂 我父亲也经常说我
I get it. Mine gets on me, too.
虽不是这种话 但也...
Not like that, but...
我想我们只是对彼此不够真正了解
I guess we don't really know that much about each other.
应该说 大多数吧
About most of you, really.
我先来坦白一下 你们都不知道的我的事
Well, I'll confess something that none of you know about me.
我跟很多人上床
I have a lot of sex.
斯蒂西 我们都知道的
Yeah, we know, Stacie.
因为我刚告诉了你
Only 'cause I just told you.
这个方法很好
This is a good idea.
这事不怎么好 不过这个方法很不错
That was a pretty bad example, but this is a good idea.
我们不如就坐成一圈
Why don't we all go around the room,
然后跟大家说说 别人所不了解的自己
and we can all say something about ourselves that nobody else knows.
我也些事情要说
Okay, I got something.
跟各位承认这事很不容易
This is hard for me to admit to you guys.
我想大家都知道是什么事了 坦诚说吧
I think we all know where this is going. Let's be honest.
这两年 我一直沉迷于
Well, for the last two years, I've had a serious
赌博
gambling problem.
- 什么?  - 什么?
- What?  - What?
自从我跟我女朋友分手之后就开始了
It started when I broke up with my girlfriend.
噢! 就是这事了
Whoomp! There it is.
我还爱你
I still love you.
还有谁吗?
Anyone else?
我在子宫里的时候 吃掉了自己的胞姐
I ate my twin in the womb.
什么?
What?
好了
Okay.
胖艾米?
Fat Amy?
我哪还有什么秘密
I'm an open book.
我的意思是 大家不都已经叫我胖艾米了嘛
I mean, for God's sake, you guys all call me Fat Amy.
我想如果我不是百分百诚实 就不算真的在活着
See, I guess I'm just not really living if I'm not being 100 % honest.
其实我的真名叫胖帕特丽夏
And my real name is Fat Patricia.
什么?
What?
好了 我以前一直都没什么
Okay. I've never been one of those girls
女性朋友 但我现在有了
who had a lot of friends who were girls. And I do now.
这样感觉真好
And that's pretty cool.
这就是我啦 下一个吧
So, that's me. Someone else please go.
好吧
Okay.
春假时 我做了一个勇敢的决定 切除我的声带小结
Over spring break, I made the courageous decision to remove my nodes.
我知道 医生说 我也许永远不能再唱
I know. The doctor said that I can't sing above a G-sharp,
升G调以上的音了
maybe ever.
我当时以为这个赛季结束了
I thought the season was over.
没事 没事的
It's okay. It's okay.
贝卡 我们该怎么办?
Beca, what do we do?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
那就别在这儿唱了
Maybe not here.
好了 我们开始混音吧
All right. Let's remix this business.
奥布里 能为我们选首歌吗?
Aubrey, would you pick a song for us, please?
布鲁诺・马尔斯的"皆应是你"
Bruno Mars, Just The Way You Are.
好的 克洛伊 你可以起个头吗?
Okay. Chloe, are you okay to take the lead?
好
Yeah.
伸出手
Hands in.
一 二...
One, two...
什么声音?
What was that?
不知道 我从未发出过这个音
I don't know, I've never made that sound before.
不过你现在医治过的声带 可以唱低音了
Yo, but with your messed up vocal cords, you could hit the bass notes.
你知道这代表什么吗?
Do you know what that means?
莉莉 怎么了?
Yes, Lilly?
我想这样我有技巧可以帮到大家
I think I have something that can help us out.
亲爱的 不需要你大声喊的
Excuse me, bitch, you don't need to shout.
可别说大话啊
Okay, don't get mouthy.
欢迎来到2012
Welcome to the finals
大学生无伴奏合唱国际锦标赛
of the 2012 International Championship of Collegiate A Cappella.
林肯中心今晚蓬荜生辉 正是因为有了这群
Lincoln Center is proud to welcome back all of these young hopefuls tonight
用嘴巴创造音乐的年轻人 他们都希望获得今晚的冠军
who are hoping to win a trophy by making music with their mouths.
盖尔 我跟你说 今晚将是美好的一晚
This is gonna be a big night, and I tell you, Gail,
- 闭上眼睛  - 我已经闭了
- if you can just shut your eyes. - I'm doing it.
闭上眼睛 忘掉什么规则
Shut your eyes and get rid of all the a-ca-politics,
只要记住 在纽约城的林肯中心
then you can remember that being at Lincoln Center, in the Big Apple,
在这个历史悠久的舞台上演唱 是每个无伴奏演唱者的梦想
and singing on this storied stage is the dream of every a cappella singer.
你说对了 约翰
You said it, John.
感谢弗吉尼亚大学喧嚣合唱团的表演 女士们先生们
The University of Virginia Hullabahoos, Iadies and gentlemen.
终于到了
There they are.
一 二 三 加油!
One, two, three, swag!
欢迎回到大学生无伴奏合唱国际锦标赛
Welcome back to the International Championship of Collegiate A Cappella.
下一支队伍 不介绍相信各位也了解了 不过我还是要介绍一下!
This next group, they need no introduction, but I'll do it anyway!
嘿
Hey.
祝你们好运
Good luck.
谢了 你们也是
Thanks. You, too.
巴顿大学的刺儿头小子合唱团!
The Barden University Treblemakers!
噢 刺儿头小子的结尾一如既往的精彩
Oh, the Trebles closing it strong like always.
非常棒 今晚很难有其他队伍超越他们了
Absolutely tight. It's gonna be very hard to beat that tonight.
其他队伍也有他们精心准备的作品 约翰
Every other group has their work cut out for them, John.
盖尔 很高兴我们不用去竞争了 谢天谢地 那种日子结束啦
I'm glad it's not us anymore, Gail. Those days are over, thank goodness.
特别是他们不要我们回去后
Especially since they wouldn't have us back.
好了 表演如何?
All right. How about that?
巴顿大学的刺儿头小子合唱团
The Barden University Treblemakers.
我爱你们 三八们
I love you, awesome nerds.
你们是最棒的
Yeah, you guys are the best.
虽然你们有些人特别瘦 不过我相信 你们都有一颗胖胖的心
Even though some of you are pretty thin, I think that you all have fat hearts,
那就足够了
and that's what matters.
我们加油吧 好吗?
Okay, let's just smash this. Okay?
女士们先生们 有请巴顿贝拉合唱团!
Ladies and gentlemen, the Barden Bellas!
噢 天啊 看到了吗?
Oh, my goodness gracious. Will you look at this?
贝拉的制服竟然不见了 她们有了新的面貌
Gone are those Bella uniforms and this is a whole new look for them,
真是正点 正点 正点
and it is hot, hot, hot.
约翰 她们让我都想变男人了
John, these girls could turn me.
我们爱你 贝拉!
We love you, Bellas!
一 二 三 四
One, two, three, four.
干得好 贝卡!
Way to go, Beca!
这场演出太精彩了!
What a show!
约翰 我想我们刚刚见证了一段无伴奏合唱的历史
I think we have just seen some a cappella history being made, John.
而且是来自一个全女生的团体啊 盖尔 我从未预见到这种情况
And from an all-female group, Gail. I could never have called this one.
当然了 你内心一直厌恶女生
Never. Well, you are a misogynist at heart,
你也自然不可能料想到这群女孩会赢
so there's no way you would have bet on these girls to win.
确实啊
Absolutely.
是不是很不可思议? 哇!
Weren't they incredible? Wow!
女士们先生们 让我们再次为巴顿贝拉鼓掌!
Ladies and gentlemen, let's give it up again for the Barden Bellas!
早告诉过你 结尾才是最精彩的
Told you. Endings are the best part.
你真是个怪胎
You're such a weirdo.
6个月后
听着 无伴奏演唱评委
Listen up, a-ca-ballers.
我曾被军队拒绝 曾被强行装进"爱探险的朵拉"背包里
I have been rejected by the Army, shoved into a Dora the Explorer backpack,
曾被推进女生的更衣室 当时除了吊裤带 什么都没穿
and pushed into the girls' locker room wearing nothing but suspenders.
不过没关系 我还在我爱的这个世界
But no matter. I am in the world that I love.
我带着我的助理 贾斯汀...
And with the assistance of my boy, Justin...
君主陛下
My liege.
我宣布今年的面试开始
I launch this year's auditions.
拍肚子
Belly roll.
最新一届的ICCA冠军将选择这首面试曲目
The most recent ICCA national champion winners get to pick the audition song.
好了 怪胎们 那就唱...
All right, nerds. Let's go with...
-=圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/=-
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 景鲤
翻译: 脸圆圆 我是羊 为化工攒人品 岸
校对: fabulous_carr 嘿疯
因为我长了声带小结
Because I have nodes.
克洛伊 别担心 只是上帝在惩罚你 因为你太漂亮太优秀了
Chloe, don't worry, it's just God punishing you 'cause you're a ginger.